[theme music playing]
[Natalie] You can't live
without your wife.
[Raul] Trust me.
If you trust me then you need
to lie low for a while.
Natalie, you're in danger.
[Claire] If Jaguar is an enemy,
why'd he let Emilia go?
[Julio] To send a message
that we are at his mercy.
I won't allow the collusion of Diego
or some hotsie-patootsie woman
like Natalie
to ruin the name Ardiente.
[Ivy] Is Diego working with Jaguar?
If they continue to work together,
I might lose the election.
[Raul] It's just gonna be the two of us.
[Julio] Should you get the chance,
I want you to kill that SOB,
so I won't have any more problems.
[Emilia] But with one condition.
You will allow me
to replace you in Congress.
[Camia] Does that mean Diego can go free?
Only if he agrees to my offer,
to tap Jaguar as his financier
in the election.
I'd rather rot in prison
than become Jaguar's lapdog.
I'll find a way to free Diego.
But first, I need to find out
the identity of Jaguar.
[Julio] You will all grace
a public appearance.
I don't want another scandal tomorrow,
so behave. Especially you, Emilia.
[Emilia] Let's look for a place
without trashes lying around.
-You're the trash here!
-Shut up!
[Camia] Your family's downfall
is within reach.
We will win this election!
[Diego] I need to get out of here.
I'm dragging Aunt Camia in this mess.
[Arnaldo] I promise you,
I will save our position.
I'll take care of our name.
The Ardientes will continue
to rule this town.
-Oh.
-Wow!
He's got taste, Auntie.
[Claire] And the other one?
-Ah!
-[chuckles]
I don't know, Emilia.
But that Jaguar seems shady.
He's like a guard dog stalking you.
And he knows what you want.
But you know, Auntie,
I like a man who knows
how to please his woman.
Goodness.
You're falling for that
masked creature, Emilia.
[laughing] Of course not, Auntie.
It's the other way around.
He is falling for me.
[phone chiming]
-Look who's calling.
-[chuckling]
I told you, Auntie. Let me take it.
Jaguar, Jaguar.
You just really know how to please me.
I love all the gifts.
-I love it.
-It's only for…
[voice changer] woman like you.
Oh, come on.
I know you want something
in exchange, right?
That's what I like about you, Emilia.
I can't get enough of you.
You're very smart.
What do you want from me?
I want to get a whiff of your sweet scent.
[smirks]
You're making me blush. Can you stop it?
Can you please tell me,
what exactly do you want from me?
Have you thought about my proposition?
I don't know yet.
Emilia, I'm impatient.
You never know,
someone else might catch my attention.
It's your call.
Okay fine, Jaguar.
After our kick-off campaign
and the engagement party of my son,
you'll know my decision.
And I'm sure, you won't be disappointed.
Okay, my love. I'll wait for it.
Bye, Jaguar.
How's the venue? Is everything set?
[woman] Not yet, sir.
We still don't have a sound system.
What do you mean by that?
Isn't that the first thing you should fix?
How will the people hear me
when I make a speech?
-I'm sorry.
-There you go again,
showing your incompetence. Get on it!
-[Ivy] Hon!
-[Arnaldo] Get out of my sight!
[Ivy] Hon.
What's wrong?
You're losing your temper again.
-Hon, relax.
-[smooches]
There you go. Relax, okay?
I'll try.
Hon,
everything will turn out fine tomorrow.
I promise.
-I promise you that.
-Okay.
Well, I need to meet with my designer
to try my outfit for tomorrow
because I want to look beautiful
for our engagement party tomorrow.
-Okay, you go do that.
-Okay.
Update me, okay?
-Bye, honey.
-Bye.
-Thank you, ma'am.
-All right.
-Judge Otico?
-Yes?
Who are you? Please, don't hurt me!
Please, don't hurt me!
Where are you taking me?
Please, don't hurt me.
Judge Otico?
Yes? Who are you?
Let's just say that I am the nightmare
of your boss, Jaguar.
Tell him to release Diego Torillo.
I don't need to.
Torillo already met with Jaguar.
And they've probably come up
with an agreement.
Please, let me go. Please.
Don't hurt me.
Let her out.
[Erlinda] Please, don't hurt me. Please.
Let's go!
Where are you taking me?
Please, don't hurt me.
Please, don't hurt me. Please.
Let's go to the precinct.
Jaguar says he doesn't want
to waste his time.
He's hoping you're here
to accept his offer.
I accept your offer
but on one condition.
If I win,
you will shut down
all your illegal businesses
in Ardiente.
I will give you a chance
to put up new businesses.
Legal businesses
that could help the public.
Diego, you have no right
to set conditions.
You are the one
who needs to follow his terms.
If that's the case,
tell your boss my sorry
for wasting his time.
You know,
the reason I am running
for governor here in Ardiente
is because I want to change this town,
not become a puppet
of a man who's more ruthless
than the Ardientes.
I don't know why you're so bent
on getting back at that family.
But I hope you're not doing
this simply for yourself,
but for the people
you care about the most.
As for me,
I'm doing this to bring justice
for my murdered mother,
for what they did
to my best friend's family,
and for neglecting the people of Ardiente!
And most of all, to free my dad
from their leash
and to be with the only family
that I have.
[dramatic music playing]
I want you to hang this
where everyone can see it.
Like near the stage. Take note of that.
Get on it.
Lara, did you check on Ivy?
[Lara] Uh… Sir, Miss Aguas
didn't go to the atelier.
They'll just deliver the dress
to her house.
[Ivy] Diego.
Ivy.
What are you doing here?
How's your meeting with Jaguar?
-How did you know?
-It's a long story.
I want to know
if you're getting out of here.
Ivy, we didn't come to an agreement.
If that's the case,
I'll meet him personally.
Ivy, it's too…
[Arnaldo] Who will you meet with, Ivy?
Hon, I knew it. I knew you'd come here.
Be safe.
You haven't answered my question.
Who will you talk to?
Answer me!
It's Camia Cruz.
I wanted to talk to her
to convince their party
to back out of the elections.
-And why would you do that?
-Hon, let's face the reality.
You conducted a survey, right? And what?
Diego got 82 percent
while you got 18 percent.
Hon, you're going to lose!
And I don't want you to get hurt!
You don't fight my battles, okay?!
You don't!
Hon, I'm your future wife!
Didn't you say we were a team?
So I'm just doing what's right!
I just spoke to them.
Hon, I want you to win.
[sighs] Okay.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry for hurting you.
All right, I admit that I was wrong.
I was wrong for not telling you
that I was going to see Diego
and that I wanted to talk to Camia.
Because, hon, I don't want you
to see me begging.
Because I can lower
my ego and pride for you.
Because I really want you to win, hon.
Hon, trust me, it's the only reason.
Hon, I love you so much.
That's why I'm marrying you.
Hon.
You don't believe me.
I'm getting scared.
You might get mad again.
Hon, maybe you'll get revenge
by calling off the wedding.
Hon, please don't.
Arnaldo, please don't. Please.
Don't even think of canceling the wedding.
Let's get married, hon.
I'm sorry. I won't do it again.
I'll never visit Diego again. Never.
I'll never go near him.
Hon, please don't…
Arnaldo, please. Please.
I'm going crazy. Answer me, please!
Hon, I'll go crazy
if you cancel the wedding.
-[Arnaldo] Hey! Hey!
-[Ivy] Please.
Hon.
-It's fine.
-What do you mean?
We're fine. I…
-[Ivy] Do you accept my…
-It's fine, now I understand.
I appreciate everything.
-[relieved sigh]
-[grunts reassuringly]
You love me?
I love you very much.
Arnaldo, are you sure you love me?
I love you so much.
Ivy Aguas, I love you so much.
-Thanks, hon.
-[Arnaldo] It may be crazy but…
-I'm also crazily in love with you.
-No, trust me, I'm crazier.
I'm going crazy, Arnaldo.
I love you so much. Thank you.
Thanks, hon.
[Arnaldo] Who will you meet with, Ivy?
Hon.
Be safe.
Just accept the Jaguar's help.
I assure you won't regret it.
[tense music]
[woman] Hello, everyone!
Vote for the mayor!
Mayor Ardiente is expecting you!
You're all invited!
Please be there! Everyone is invited!
[woman] What's this new gimmick
of the mayor?
Maybe a pronouncement of another lie.
Yeah, right.
[woman] Let's vote for Mayor Arnaldo!
Let's show our support!
A great leader of this town!
-[woman] Support the Ardientes!
-An event hosted by the family!
-Don't miss it!
-Come on!
Everyone!
We have an invitation
from the rival party.
-[Pandoy] What?
-They said we shouldn't miss it.
If you think that your event
will be a success, Ardientes,
well…
[chuckling]
…you're all wrong.
Very wrong.
[door squeaks]
-Grandpa, you wanted to see me?
-Hi.
Arnaldo, tomorrow is your big day.
And I'm sure you're going
to make me proud.
I will.
I do feel the pressure
but I'll do my best.
Anyway, that's not the only reason
why I summoned you.
What I have here in my hand
is an heirloom.
It's very important to me.
This used to belong
to your great-grandmother.
Now,
I want you to present this
to Ivy as an engagement ring.
Wow!
[smirks] Thank you.
Don't thank me yet.
You still have an election to win.
[tense music]
[dripping]
[Diego] What do you want from me?
Why are you helping me?
Jaguar says he will help you
in your candidacy
by providing money,
personnel, and arsenals.
And Diego, he also guarantees
your victory against Arnaldo.
[Ivy] Don't worry, Diego.
Mom and I will do everything
to get you out of prison.
I won't let Arnaldo hurt you.
Please stay safe.
Wow!
My wife looks stunning today.
Your heels and necklace suit you.
That's ruby, isn't it? Your birthstone.
[Emilia] Arnaldo, where's Ivy?
Ivy will meet us at the venue.
Grandpa is waiting outside. So, let's go?
-Our supporters are waiting.
-Let's go.
-[crowd chattering]
-[brass music playing]
[Arnaldo] I expect your support
in the election.
Thank you so much.
That's what I like.
I always see you around.
Thank you so much for gracing my events.
[Arnaldo laughing] That's great.
Really great.
-We'll further boost it.
-[man] Yeah.
[Arnaldo] Yeah, good.
The other party has no match against me.
I am rightful to serve, not those…
[men] Julio! Julio! Julio! Julio!
Julio! Julio! Julio! Julio!
Julio! Julio!
Terrific! Thanks.
Hon!
-You look beautiful.
-[Ivy] Thank you.
Are you ready?
I'll publicly introduce you
as the future first lady
of Poblacion Ardiente.
-[brass music playing]
-[people cheering]
Everyone, let us all welcome
-Congressman Julio Ardiente!
-[crowd applauding]
[emcee] Former Governor
Emilia Ardiente-Torillo
and her husband, Mister Raul Torillo.
-Miss Clarita de Guzman.
-[crowd applauding]
-Miss Ivy Aguas.
And of course, our beloved mayor
and the future governor
of Poblacion Ardiente,
Mayor Arnaldo Ardiente-Torillo!
-[crowd cheering loudly]
-[brass music playing]
[Arnaldo] Everyone,
please take your seats.
-[chuckles]
-[woman] I love you, Mayor!
-I love you too!
-[crowd cheering]
[Arnaldo] Good morning,
Poblacion Ardiente!
[crowd applauding]
I am extremely glad that you've joined us
for this very important event.
I love you all
that's why I want you all to be part
of my life as your future governor.
[crowd applauding]
Today, let me introduce to all of you
your future first lady.
She is the woman who captured my heart.
The woman who continuously
makes the Ardientes stronger!
Everyone,
my most beloved lady, Ivy Aguas!
[crowd cheering loudly]
[tense music playing]
Please.
Hon, I know I already proposed to you,
but it would be even better
if the people of Ardiente
witnessed this moment
[applause, crowd cheering]
If it's okay with you,
I'd like to ask for your hand once again
in front of our supporters.
[crowd cheering]
Ivy Aguas,
[crowd clapping]
I love you so much.
[crowd cheering]
Will you marry me?
-[crowd cheering louder]
-[Arnaldo laughs]
-Yes! Yes!
-Yes!
[crowd cheering]
[woman] Viva Ardiente!
[shutter clicks]
[crowd cheering]
[Arnaldo] Flowers for you, of course.
[shutter clicks]
Viva Ardiente!
[crowd] Viva Ardiente!
[brass music playing]
-Congratulations, Governor.
-Thank you. Thank you.
[brass music playing]
Viva Ardiente!
[Arnaldo] Okay, I have more
good news for you.
Now, I'll share with you
my provincial platforms!
[woman] You're only going
to manipulate us,
just like what you did to that woman!
[crowd booing]
[Arnaldo] Ahh…
These projects we'll be?
[Diego] Instead of public service,
you'll only make them suffer!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
What now?! Were you surprised?!
Yes, I'm a free man now!
And you can never imprison me again!
It's your family
that needs to be imprisoned!
You will go down!
And a new Ardiente will be reborn
that is governed by the people!
For a new Ardiente!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego.
This event and the public governance
are only for the worthy,
not for ex-convicts like you.
Lies!
The Court is the one who absolved me.
I was never sentenced,
so I'm not an ex-convict!
What about you, Arnaldo?!
When will you go to prison
for all the crimes that you committed?!
[crowd murmuring]
-Diego! Diego!
-Boo!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego has been freed?
Doesn't that mean he agreed
to the terms of Jaguar?!
Let's not get ahead of ourselves.
What's important
is that Diego is free now.
The rightful future governor
has been freed.
Miss Camia is right.
[Arnaldo] Crimes?
What crimes are you talking about?
[crowd] Yeah, right!
You tried to kill me inside the jail,
and worst is you killed Nimfa Naig!
-That's true!
-[crowd] Yeah, right!
Boo!
[crowd clamoring]
There's no evidence
to support your accusations!
We are not stupid!
We all know
that the Ardientes hold
the law in this land!
-[Arnaldo chuckles]
-[crowd clamoring]
Says the man who's supposed
to be in prison but is now free!
Maybe you're the one who's abusing power?
-[crowd] Yeah, right!
-[Arnaldo] Now what?
Diego, my little brother,
stop spreading lies.
I didn't know you came here
just to crack jokes.
[chuckles]
Laugh while you can, Arnaldo.
Because once I kick you out
of the capitol,
I'll make sure to deal with you first!
I'll serve justice and punishment
for all your crimes!
[crowd clamoring]
Yeah, that's right!
The Ardientes should pay
for all their crimes!
Diego for Governor!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego!
[screams]
Arrest that criminal!
[Camia] You have no right to arrest Diego!
He's innocent! Fight him fair and square!
Shut up!
You damn trespassers! Get the hell out!
We're residents of this town!
We were invited!
[crowd] That's right!
Diego! Diego!
I don't care! Shut up!
-[crowd] Diego! Diego!
-[Arnaldo] Get out!
-Hon!
-[crowd] Diego! Diego!
[Ivy] Hon! No! Let go!
Hon!
Shut up!
Silence, all of you!
What are you so smug about?
Is this the future of Poblacion Ardiente?!
A town full of unruly citizens?!
You uncivilized people!
You said you were invited!
What for?! To cause ruckus?!
Is this the kind of future
you want for your kids?!
Are you really the future leaders
of this province?!
You will do anything
for the throne and power!
You better look in the mirror
before you criticize!
You damn hypocrites!
[derisive scoff]
Arnaldo! Let's go!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
No!
[crowd] Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego! Diego!
Lara, issue a press release
denying everything that happened
in that stupid charade!
But, Congressman, the news is everywhere.
The only way to turn this around
is to apologize
to the camp of Diego Torillo
for poking that gun.
Apologize?!
[smirks] Yeah, right!
And the moon that's hanging up there
is made out of cheese!
What's wrong with you?!
There's no gun pointing!
Arnaldo did not point his gun!
He didn't do anything wrong!
It's their word against ours!
And their words don't matter anyway.
[chuckles]
Here comes Lady Godiva on her high horse.
[Lara] Excuse me, sir.
Well, Emilia, where is your son?!
Well, your favorite grandson
is still sleeping.
The reputation of Arnaldo
is already ruined, Papa.
Why won't you let me run
for governor, instead?
Emilia, please! Stay out of this.
Because no matter what happens,
Arnaldo, your son,
is a hundred times
better a choice for governor
than you will ever be.
So, please, just do what you have to do!
Okay, Papa. I will wake him up.
Diego shouldn't have gotten out of prison.
The evidence is rock solid.
It's perfectly planned.
He shouldn't have gotten out.
Oh, Honey, let's go.
We're going to be late for our meeting.
Are you happy?
Happy?
Are you happy that Diego is now free?
[smirks]
See.
That's what I've been asking myself.
Why are you always ambiguous
when it comes to my lovely brother?
Why can't you just pick a side?
My side!
Is that difficult?
Honey.
You know that I believe in you.
[Ivy] I believe that you will fall soon.
I did everything to win.
[mumbling] I did everything…
[Ivy] Just a little more evidence
will secure your loss.
DIEGO FOR THE NEW ARDIENTE
You were right.
I accepted the support of Jaguar.
[somber music playing]
Diego, you know what Jaguar
wants in return.
He's going to control you.
But he doesn't want anything in return.
What do you mean?
[cop] Diego!
-Yes?
-[cop] Just follow me.
Your attorney didn't tell us about this.
Does she know about this?
Not yet.
Everything happened so fast.
Honestly, Diego.
Do you really think Jaguar
got you out of prison?
I'm not sure, Auntie.
But if he did, I didn't ask for it,
and I didn't agree to his terms.
But I won't deny myself this freedom.
[Loring] But what if he returns
and demands payment?
Well, whatever happens,
I'll stay out of trouble.
[Camia] Yes, you should.
And if that Jaguar really is behind this,
I hope this is the last time
he is involved with you.
It's good!
Anyway, we knew that case wouldn't stick.
But…
Diego was released earlier than expected.
Hon, if I remember correctly,
you had Diego imprisoned.
Miss Aguas!
You seem shocked!
Welcome to the world of politics.
You're not new to this.
We stop at nothing
to make sure that we win.
[in French] That's life, that's war.
Now the rest, we attribute
to collateral damage.
Ivy, why so concerned?
And may I ask you?
Who are you worried about,
Arnaldo or Diego?
[Ivy] Future mother-in-law,
you shouldn't be asking that.
Because I'm going to marry Arnaldo.
You should know the answer.
Just making sure.
[clapping] Good!
Now, where was I?
Oh! Diego!
You know, we have to show
the other side of Diego
to the voters of this town.
That Diego is not as clean
as he presents himself to be.
We should gather…
Emilia, that's your job.
…that Diego also receives help
from criminals like Jaguar,
which will make him a hypocrite and…
-a liar just like us.
-[laughing]
Yes, Papa.
If Jaguar really helped Diego,
I'm sure the two will definitely meet.
I'll take care of it, Papa.
Okay.
[Emilia] Arnaldo, are you okay?
You seem bothered again!
You're always like that!
Batch, this is our schedule
for the next two weeks.
It's crunch time as the election nears,
so we have to accomplish everything here.
Check this for approval.
-This is good, batch.
-Okay.
Have you finished the costing
of the materials we need?
-Batch, excuse me.
-[Marlon] Sure.
-Hello, Ivy.
-Diego, how are you?
Are you sure no one is hearing you?
Yeah, I'm safe. I'm at home right now.
Diego, I'm worried about you.
Ivy, I'm fine and free.
Can I meet with you?
With what happened earlier,
the Ardientes will keep their eyes on you.
By the way, I'm looking for more evidence
against the Ardientes.
Be careful.
It's you who should be more careful.
The Ardientes might use
your connections with Jaguar…
-to ruin you.
-They can't do that to me.
Just be careful.
[Julio on audio record]
Miss Aguas! You seem shocked!
You're not new to this.
We stop at nothing
to make sure that we win.
[Emilia] Who are you worried about,
Arnaldo or Diego?
[Ivy] I'm going to marry Arnaldo.
-You should know the answer.
-[Emilia] Just making sure.
[Ivy] This is not enough.
I have to make Arnaldo confess
to the crimes he committed.
[Raul] Emilia.
You look stressed again.
What's the matter?
I am stressed about Papa's task.
Task? What task? Maybe I can help you?
I need to deliver your replacement's head.
[clicks tongue] So, it's Jaguar again.
[chuckling] I'm just laughing
when you mention him.
First of all,
since when did you lower your standards?
You haven't even seen that man's face.
Suddenly, he's your type?
Emilia, that man is always wearing a mask
because he thinks he'll need it
for the rest of his life.
I bet he looks like a bug.
-Hmm.
-Right?
[laughing]
Raul, look. He gave me this.
Well, I remember on our wedding day,
you also gave me one of these.
You said you bought it with your savings.
But it turns out,
you just asked Papa for it.
But it's fine. It's still sweet, though.
So, you think this Jaguar guy
is copying me, huh?
Maybe he's imitating me
but he can't really pull it off.
First of all, his style
is different from mine,
like giving gifts.
You said it yourself,
I need to ask for money to buy you gifts.
I'm straightforward about what I want.
Like how I got you.
I don't beat around the bush
or charm you with gifts.
I tell people if I like them.
So tell me,
do you love me?
Yes.
I can't feel it, Emilia.
-I love you.
-Really?
Then kiss me.
[chuckling]
-[both chuckling]
-That's it?
[phone ringing]
-Emilia.
-Hmm?
[ringing continues]
Looks like I set the alarm wrong again.
Where are you going?
-To the salon.
-All right.
[tense music]
[Rufo] Ma'am.
[sighs]
Come on, Jaguar.
Didn't I tell you
not to make surprise visits?
But, you called, right?
Yes.
I called because I wanted to know
if you're behind the release of Diego.
Emilia, if that's the only reason
why you asked me to come,
then I'm just wasting my time.
Can you please just answer the question?!
I'll only answer
once you've decided to cooperate with me.
[Rufo] Ma'am.
What are you doing here?!
Why are you here?
Didn't your message say that
you'd leave me alone?
You're right.
I'm just assuring your safety.
Why are you doing this?
What do you want
in exchange for all this?!
The same thing you want,
the demise of the Ardientes.
I'm sure that's what you want, right?
[tense music]
[Emilia] Finally,
this will bring you down,
Diego Torillo.
[Camia] What will you do now, Lily?
How are we going to fight Arnaldo?
By force.
[Ivy] I'll drive him insane.
I will grind and break him apart.
-[Arnaldo] Leave!
-[Ivy] Stop!
[Ivy] Emilia and Julio will also go crazy
because of what's happening to Arnaldo.
Ever since you became his fiancé,
-he's started acting crazy!
-That's enough!
[Emilia] You won't attend the debate!
You'll only look like a fool, Arnaldo!
[supporters] Diego Torillo for governor!
[supporters] Viva Ardiente!
[Arnaldo] Who did this?!
[crowd clamoring]
[theme music playing]